My legs hurt...
My glasses are missing...
November 1, 06:02, Sendai Colony
Episode 54
Tokyo Colony No. 1, Part 1
Screw it,
I'll use it where I can.
The Next Day,
The Zenin Clan Is Exterminated
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days of
joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
9: Players shall be able to view the
following information on other players:
name, points, number of
rules added, current Colony.
He's actually a human who really existed,
though it was over a thousand years ago.
Sukuna?
Searching
Kashimo Hajime
Points
Rule Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 2
Higuruma Hiromi
Points
Rules Added
Current Colony: Tokyo No. 1
8: Players who do not show a
change in points within 19 days
of joining or acquiring points
shall be stripped of their technique.
Day
"Players may expend
points to leave the Culling Game."
Angel
Persuade Players with 100 Points
and No Intention of Adding a Rule
Hunt Down Kashimo Hajime
Hunt Down Higuruma Hiromi
November 11th 12:00 Tokyo
(Remaining Time Until Tsumiki
Must Enter the Culling Game:
7 Days 12 Hours)
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Boo...
Split Ahead
Next Episode
Tokyo Colony No. 1, Part 2